[
    {
        "id"            : 0,
        "category"      : "Math",
        "question"      : "8 x 5",
        "answers"       : ["40", "35", "29"],
        "correctAnswer" : "40"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 1,
        "category"      : "Math",
        "question"      : "45 x 5",
        "answers"       : ["245", "225", "250"],
        "correctAnswer" : "225"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 2,
        "category"      : "Math",
        "question"      : "12 + 13",
        "answers"       : ["22", "25", "26"],
        "correctAnswer" : "25"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 3,
        "category"      : "Math",
        "question"      : "25 * 25",
        "answers"       : ["255", "525", "625"],
        "correctAnswer" : "625"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 4,
        "category"      : "Math",
        "question"      : "52 / 4",
        "answers"       : ["13", "14", "12"],
        "correctAnswer" : "13"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 5,
        "category"      : "History",
        "question"      : "First man on the moon",
        "answers"       : ["1968", "1969", "1970"],
        "correctAnswer" : "1969"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 6,
        "category"      : "History",
        "question"      : "Colombo discovers America",
        "answers"       : ["1492", "1494", "1501"],
        "correctAnswer" : "1492"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 7,
        "category"      : "Movie",
        "question"      : "Oscars won by Forrest Gump",
        "answers"       : ["4", "5", "6"],
        "correctAnswer" : "6"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 8,
        "category"      : "Movie",
        "question"      : "Oscars won by Tom Hanks",
        "answers"       : ["1", "2", "3"],
        "correctAnswer" : "2"
    },
    {
        "id"            : 9,
        "category"      : "Movie",
        "question"      : "First Star Wars movie year",
        "answers"       : ["1977", "1979", "1981"],
        "correctAnswer" : "1977"
    }
]
